<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Darija's Art</title><link>/en/events/</link><description>Recent content on Darija's Art</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/en/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exhibition at Galleri Jan Graff</title><link>/en/events/galleri-jan-graff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/events/galleri-jan-graff/</guid><description>WHERE: Galleri Jan Graff, Radarveien 4, Karlsrud, Oslo. T.: 913 00 343, jan (at) graff.com. See a map &amp;raquo;
WHEN: 25 September -17 October, 2010. Opening hours: Sat. - Sun. 11.00–18.00, Wen. 17.00–19.00, or by agreement OPENING: 25 September, 12.00. At the opening of the exibition we hope for a nice atmosphere in these pleasant surroundings.</description></item><item><title>Exhibition in the Lithuanian Embassy</title><link>/en/events/embassy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/events/embassy/</guid><description>Where: Lithuanian Embassy, Dronningens gate 3, Oslo When: 17th Feb. – 17th March. Monday – Friday 8–16. Closed 12th March. Exhibition is held between the two National days of Lithuania. On the 11th March Lithuania is celebrating 20 years jubileum of restoration of independancy after soviet occupation. 16th Feb. and 11th March - events connected to Lithuania&amp;rsquo;s National Days. Vernissage on 16th Feb. 18.00.
Paintings: Oil paintings that are exhibited come from the series Place Norway, Place Lithuania and Simply human.</description></item><item><title>Exhibition of paintings at Dalype Gallery</title><link>/en/events/dalype/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/events/dalype/</guid><description>WHERE: Dalype Gallery, Bentsegata 1, Oslo. Dalype Gallery is located on the corner of Bentsegata and Maridalsveien in a building that is a part of the picturesque Omholt courtyard. The old cobble-stone courtyard with the surrounding houses were bought by Aage Omholt in 1940. The half-timbered houses are mainly from the 1900th century, having housed around 90 people in 1875. In 2001 the houses were designated as listed buildings by Byantikvaren.</description></item><item><title>Participation at Art:Oslo, biggest Norwegian art happening. Oslo Spektrum, 18-19 September 2010</title><link>/en/events/art-oslo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/events/art-oslo/</guid><description>WHERE: STAND A02-19, Oslo Spektrum, Sonja Henies plass 2, Oslo. Read more at Art:Oslo &amp;raquo;
WHEN: 18–19 September 2010. Open Saturday and Sunday 10:00–18:00. Art duel Saturday 13.00. ABOUT THE ART FAIR: The exhibition is aimed at art buyers and art lovers of all ages, where they will meet the artists and hear about their ideas and the work that lies behind their artworks. The artists decide all activities in the stage and cafe area, such as auctions, painting competitions etc.</description></item></channel></rss>